const questionBank = [
  {
    question: 'The default value of "position" attribute is _______',
    options: ['Fixed', 'Absolute', 'Static', 'Relative'],
    answer: 'Static',
  },
  {
    question: 'Everything in React is a ___________',
    options: ['Module', 'Component', 'Package', 'Class'],
    answer: 'Component',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many elements does a react component return?',
    options: ['One', 'Two', 'Multiple', 'None'],
    answer: 'Multiple',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is state in React?',
    options: ['A persistant storage', 'An internal data of a component'],
    answer: 'An internal data of a component',
  },

  {
    question: 'What is Babel?',
    options: [
      'A transpiler',
      'An interpreter',
      'A Compiler',
      'Both Compiler and Transpilar',
    ],
    answer: 'Both Compiler and Transpilar',
  },
  {
    question: 'In React what is used to pass data to a component from outside?',
    options: ['setState', 'render with arguments', 'props', 'PropTypes'],
    answer: 'props',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a react.js in MVC?',
    options: ['Middleware', 'Controller', 'Model', 'Router'],
    answer: 'Controller',
  },
  {
    question: 'ReactJS uses _____ to increase performance',
    options: ['Original DOM', 'Virtual DOM', 'Both 1 & 2', 'None'],
    answer: 'Virtual DOM',
  },
  {
    question: 'React.js Covers only the view layer of the app.',
    options: ['Yes', 'No'],
    answer: 'Yes',
  },
  {
    question:
      '.............. helps react for keeping their data unidirectional.',
    options: ['JSX', 'Flux', 'Dom', 'Props'],
    answer: 'Flux',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who Develop React.js?',
    options: ['Apple', 'Facebook', 'Twitter', 'Google'],
    answer: 'Facebook',
  },
  {
    question: 'When was the JavaScript library first released?',
    options: ['2013', '2014', '2015', '2017'],
    answer: '2013',
  },
  {
    question: 'What can you develop on React?',
    options: [
      'Cryptocurrency',
      'Applications',
      'User interfaces',
      'Mini-games',
    ],
    answer: 'User interfaces',
  },
  {
    question: 'What does the library aim to provide out of the following?',
    options: ['Stability', 'Longevity', 'Scalability', 'Precision'],
    answer: 'Scalability',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the production size of the library?',
    options: ['90KiB', '220KiB', '109KiB', '150KiB'],
    answer: '109KiB',
  },
];

export default questionBank;
